Guide to the Time Inc. The March of Time Audiovisual Collection 1979-1995 MS 3009-RG 15
New-York Historical Society
- Series II. Commercially Distributed Audiovisual Materials [RESTRICTED], 1987-1988, undated; 1.5 Linear feet in 2 record cartons
  - The March of Time: Postwar Problems and Solutions: Special Collector's Edition Box Set, 1987-1988 (Offsite-box 2810, Item 7)
    1 videocassette (VHS) (125 min): 1/2 in. Title: "The March of Time Presents Post-War Problems and Solutions America's Post-War Problems Part 1"
    1 videocassette (VHS) (119 min): 1/2 in. Title: "The March of Time Presents Post-War Problems and Solutions America's Post-War Problems Part 2"
    1 videocassette (VHS) (107 min): 1/2 in. Title: "The March of Time Presents Post-War Problems and Solutions Post-War Problems Beyond Part 1"
    1 videocassette (VHS) (125 min): 1/2 in. Title: "The March of Time Presents Post-War Problems and Solutions Post-War Problems Beyond Part 2)
    1 videocassette (VHS) (120 min): 1/2 in. Title: "The March of Time Presents Post-War Problems and Solutions Modern Main Stree, U.S.A."
  - The March of Time: Trouble Abroad: Special Collector's Edition Box Set, 1987-1988 (Offsite-box 2811, Item 1)
    1 videocassette (VHS) (71 min.): 1/2 in. Title: "The March of Time Presents Trounle Abroad 1937-1939 War Abroad: Depression at Home 1937 Part 1". Includes a note: "Vol. IV Issue #1 War In China Sept. 1937"
    1 videocassette (VHS) (76 min.): 1/2 in. Title: "The March of Time Presents Trouble Abroad 1937-1939 Tension Increase 1937 Part 2"
    1 videocassette (VHS) (93 min.): 1/2 in. Title: "The March of Time Presents Trouble Abroad 1937-1939 Germany and Other Problems 1938 Prt 3"
    1 videocassette (VHS) (91 min.): 1/2 in. Title: "The March of Time Presents Trouble Abroad 1937-1939 Spotlight on War 1938 Part 4"
    1 videocassette (VHS) (75 min.): 1/2 in. Title: "The March of Time Presents Trouble Abroad 1937-1939 Uncle Sam: The Observer 1938-1939 Part 5"
    1 videocassette (VHS) (91 min.): 1/2 in. Title: "The March of Time Presents Trouble Abroad 1937-1939 War, Peace and America 1939 Part 6"
  - The March of Time: War Breaks Out: Special Collector's Edition Box Set, 1987 (Offsite-box 2811, Item 2)
    1 videocassette (VHS) (118 min.): 1/2 in. Title: "The March of Time Presents War Breaks Out Americans Prepare Part 1"
    1 videocassette (VHS) (113 min.): 1/2 in. Title: "The March of Time Presents War Breaks Out Americans Prepare Part 2"
    1 videocassette (VHS) (107 min.): 1/2 in. Title: "The March of Time Presents War Breaks Out The Battle Beyond Part 1"
    1 videocassette (VHS) (117 min.): 1/2 in. Title: "The March of Time Presents War Breaks Out The Battle Beyond Part 2"
    1 videocassette (VHS) (124 min.): 1/2 in. Title: "The March of Time Presnts War Breaks Out The Military Prepares"
    1 videocassette (VHS) (71 min.): 1/2 in. Title: "The March of Time Presents War Breaks Out Praying for Peace"
  - WPA Film Library Sample Reel, undated (Offsite-box 2811, Item 3)